ACWA Hyman Blumberg Memorabilia 6015 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACWA Hyman Blumberg Memorabilia
1916-1960
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA)
Blumberg, Hyman
6015 MB
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Memorabilia.
7120847
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 14, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 13, 2015
Scope and Contents
Many convention badges, lots of newspaper clippings deteriorating conditions. 1? In hebrew. Photos are in plastic covered pages of albums or rolled up due to lack of support. Many books are duplicates of library mateirals and Center rare items. Few are novel additions.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619 mf: ACWA Records Parts 1-3 on Microfilm 5868 mf: Joseph Schlossberg Additional Papers on Microfilm 5110: Jacob Billikopf New York City Men's Clothing Industry Arbiration Case Files 5670: ACWA Organizer Ida Alter Diaries 5674 OHM: ACWA Master Tapes of Interviews with Retirees 5674 OHT: ACWA Transcripts of Interviews with Retirees 5744: ACTWU Newsclipping Files regarding J.P. Stevens Boycott 5743 P: ACWA Photographs 5107: Decision of the Boards Regarding Hart, Schaffner & Marx, Chicago Industrial Federation of Clothing Manufacturers 5665 mf: ACTWU Fall River Local Minute Books on Microfilm 6015: ACWA Hyman Blumberg Records 6015 P: ACWA Hyman Blumberg Photographs
Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Blumberg, Hyman, 1885-1968; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives
7120847
- CIO Badges - 1944-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  6 pieces
- CIO Badges - 1952-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- CIO Badges - 1944-1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- CIO Badges - 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  5 pieces
- CIO Badges - 1940-1943 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- District Council No. 3 - Badges (Box 1, Folder 6)
  2 pieces
- ACWA Badges - AFL-CIO Badges (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Medallions, coins, buttons, pins - CIO (Box 1, Folder 8)
  20 pieces
- ACWA Badges, AFL-CIO Badge, FDR pin (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ACWA Badges - 1926-1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  8 pieces
- ACWA Badges (Box 1, Folder 11)
  7 pieces
- ACWA Badges - 1916-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ACWA Badges - 1926-1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ACWA Badges - 1920-1940 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ACWA Badges - 1924-1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Misc. Buttons & Pins (Box 1, Folder 16)
- CIO Badges (Box 1, Folder 17)
- ACWA Badge 1918; New York Joint Board Sash 1940 (Box 1, Folder 18)